Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Assistant Files, 1965-2011; III.
  - Suzanne Spaulding, 1981-1987; 42.
    - Foreign affairs, Nuclear weapons, 1985-1986 (Box 470, Folder 11)
    - Foreign affairs, Population control, 1984-1986 (Box 470, Folder 12)
    - Foreign affairs, Soviet competition, 1982-1985 (Box 470, Folder 13)
    - Foreign affairs, Sri Lanka, Taiwan, and the Koreas, 1983-1985 (Box 470, Folder 14)
    - Public relations, 1984-1985 (Box 470, Folder 15-16)
    - Public relations, 1984-1985 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Public relations, Computer crime, 1983 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Public relations, Crime speeches (Box 471, Folder 3-4)
    - Public relations, Immigration, 1984-1986 (Box 471, Folder 5-6)
    - Public relations, Mass mailings, 1983-1986 (Box 471, Folder 7-8)
    - Public relations, Mass mailings, Business, civil rights, 1983-1986 (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - Public relations, Mass mailings, Environment, Social Security, veterans, 1983-1986 (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - Public relations, Media and news, 1984-1986 (Box 471, Folder 11-14)
    - Public relations, National Violent Crime Program, 1983-1984 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Public relations, Three Mile Island, 1985 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Public relations, Vigilantism, 1985 (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Public relations, Women's Bar Association, 1981-1982 (Box 472, Folder 4)
  - Josh Stull, 1998-2007; 43.
    Josh Stull served as legislative assistant (agriculture, labor), 2006-2008.
    - Labor issues (Box 472, Folder 5-7)
    - Mine safety, 2006-2007 (Box 472, Folder 8-10)
    - Minimum wage in American Samoa, 2007 (Box 472, Folder 11)
    - Postal reform, 1998-2003 (Box 472, Folder 12)
  - Scott Trew, 2003-2004; 44.
    Scott Trew worked in Senator Specter's office, with materials dated 2003-2004.
    - Senate hearings, 9/11 families reform, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 13)
    - Senate hearings, Diploma mills, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 14)
    - Senate hearings, Empowering informed financial decisions, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 15)
    - Senate hearings, Government purchase cards, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 16)
    - Senate hearings, Postal reform, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 17)
    - Senate hearings, Postal reform, Joint Senate-House, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 18)
    - Senate hearings, Postal reform, Mailing industry, 2004 (Box 472, Folder 19)
    - Senate hearings, Postal service, 2003-2004 (Box 472, Folder 20)
    - Senate hearings, Postal service, Workforce issues, 2004 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Senate hearings, Terrorism financing, 2004 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Senate hearings, Reorganizing intelligence community, 2004 (Box 473, Folder 3)
  - Doug Troutman, 1984-1997; 45.
    Doug Troutman served as legislative correspondent (governmental affairs, housing, urban affairs), 1993-1996.
    - BIF-SAIF, 1995 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Budget reconciliation, 1990 (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Capital gains, 1995 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Constituent requests, 1995-1996 (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Constituent requests, Canadian lumber subsidies, 1992-1994 (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Constituent requests, Cove Shoe Company, 1991-1995 (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Constituent requests, Flowline Corporation, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Constituent requests, Hamburg Broom Works NAFTA complaint, 1996 (Box 473, Folder 11)
    - Harkin Amendment, 1992-1994 (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - H. R. 1074, Duty Suspension Bill, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - H. R. 4603, Reemployment Act, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - International Trade Commission (ITC) appointment, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - OECD Shipbuilding Agreement, 1995 (Box 473, Folder 17)
    - S. 320, Export Admin. Authorization Act, 1991 (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - S. 332, Materials against GATT violation charge, 1993-1995 (Box 473, Folder 19)
    - S. 650, Community Reinvestment Act, 1995 (Box 473, Folder 20)
    - S. 783, Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 21)
    - S. 990, Shipbuilding Trade Reform Act, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 22)
    - S. 1063, Football Coaches Technical Correction Act, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 23)
    - S. 1086, American-owned Family Business Act, 1986-1995 (Box 473, Folder 24)
    - S. 1275, Fair Trade, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 25)
    - S. 1275, Baker amendment, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 26)
    - S. 1347, Lead Abatement Trust Fund Act, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 27)
    - S. 1361, Shipbuilding and Repair Act, 1991-1994 (Box 473, Folder 28)
    - S. 1398, Contributions in Aid of Construction, 1993 (Box 473, Folder 29)
    - S. 1498, Business Meal & Entertainment Deductibility, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 30)
    - S. 1610, Independent Contractor Tax Simplification Act, 1996 (Box 473, Folder 31)
    - S. 1898, Publicly traded stock gifts to private foundations, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 32)
    - S. 1945, Maritime and Securities Trade Act, 1994 (Box 473, Folder 33)
    - S. 1963, Interstate Banking and Branching, 1994 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - S. 1984, Specter/Domenici Bill, 1991-1993 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - S. 2957, Rural Land Conservation Act, 1992-1995 (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Social Security, 1995-1997 (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - Statements on budget reconciliation, 1993 (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - Trade, Binational Dispute Panel, 1993 (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - Trade, Ceramic tile industry Pennsylvania, 1984-1991 (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - Trade, Defense Nuclear Agency, 1992-1994 (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Japanese trade barriers, 1992-1994 (Box 474, Folder 9)
    - Trade, Memos, 1992-1995 (Box 474, Folder 10)
    - Trade, Positions, 1995 (Box 474, Folder 11)
    - Trade, Super IRA and deficit, 1993-1994 (Box 474, Folder 12)
    - Trade, Unlisted Trading Privileges rule changes, 1994 (Box 474, Folder 13)
    - Trade, White House Conference on Small Business, 1995 (Box 474, Folder 14)
    - Voting record, 1995-1997 (Box 474, Folder 15)
    - Workforce Security Act, 1994 (Box 474, Folder 16)
  - Scott Waitlevertch, 1987-1995; 46.
    Scott Waitlevertch served as: legislative correspondent, 1990; and legislative assistant, 1991-1993.
    - Nominations, 1993 (Box 474, Folder 17)
    - Veterans, 1987-1991 (Box 474, Folder 18)
    - Veterans, 1992-1993 (Box 474, Folder 19)
    - Veterans (Box 474, Folder 20-22)
  - James Warner, 1997-2010; 47.
    James Warner worked in Senator Specter's office, with materials dated 1997-2010.
    - Air Products and Chemicals (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - Bingaman-Specter discussion draft, 2007 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - Building STAR, 2010 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Coal Council, 2009 (Box 475, Folder 4)
    - Coal ash, 2009-2010 (Box 475, Folder 5)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 1997-1998 (Box 475, Folder 6)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 1999-2004 (Box 475, Folder 7)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 2004-2005 (Box 475, Folder 8)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 2005-2007 (Box 475, Folder 9-15)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 2007 (Box 475, Folder 16)
    - Coal to Clean Fuels Project, 2007 (Box 476, Folder 1-3)
    - Cogentrix Energy, 2009 (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Copenhagen, 2009-2010 (Box 476, Folder 5)
    - CAFE, 2007-2008 (Box 476, Folder 6-8)
    - Cost containment, 2009 (Box 476, Folder 9)
    - Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box 476, Folder 10)
    - Energy appropriations, 2009 (Box 476, Folder 11-13)
    - Energy-Intensive Trade-Exposed Industries, 2009 (Box 476, Folder 14)
    - Environmental meetings and memos, 2010 (Box 476, Folder 15)
    - EPA authority, 2009-2010 (Box 476, Folder 16)
    - EPA lead paint requirements, 2010 (Box 476, Folder 17)
    - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 2010 (Box 476, Folder 18)
    - Gasoline price bill, 2008 (Box 476, Folder 19)
    - Gasoline price bill, 2008 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Grants, 2003-2006 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Johnson Controls, 2010 (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Mack Trucks, undated (Box 477, Folder 4)
    - Marjol Battery Site, 2001-2004 (Box 477, Folder 5-6)
    - Memos, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 7)
    - National Brownfields Coalition (Box 477, Folder 8)
    - National Conservation, Environment and Energy Independence Act, 2008 (Box 477, Folder 9-11)
    - National Rural Electric Cooperative Association, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 12)
    - Natural gas, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 14)
    - Nicholas Institute, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 15)
    - Office policy, 2006-2008 (Box 477, Folder 16)
    - Penn State, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania Coal Coalition, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission (Box 477, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania state government, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 20)
    - PJM, 2008 (Box 477, Folder 21)
    - PPL, 2009-2010 (Box 477, Folder 22)
    - Preemption, undated (Box 477, Folder 23)
    - Religion and global warming, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 24)
    - Renewable Energy Marketers Association, 2009 (Box 477, Folder 25)
    - Southwestern Energy, undated (Box 477, Folder 26)
    - Steel, 2007-2010 (Box 477, Folder 27)
    - Strategic Energy Efficiency and Renewables Reserve, 2006-2007 (Box 477, Folder 28)
    - Tranguch oil spill, 2002-2004 (Box 477, Folder 29-30)
    - Tranguch oil spill, 2002-2004 (Box 478, Folder 1-2)
    - United Mine Workers, 2010 (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - United Refining, undated (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Climate Action Network, 2009 (Box 478, Folder 5)
    - US Conference of Mayors, 2009 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - United Steel Workers, 2009 (Box 478, Folder 7)
    - Waxman-Markey, 2009 (Box 478, Folder 8)
- Activities, 1981-2009; IV.
  The Activities series contains information about specific legialtive activities that Senator Specter was involved in. This includes information on President Bill Clinton's 1998-1999 impeachment trial, floor statements, and voting records. The files contain Congressional Records, voting reports, correspondence, and hearing transcripts.
  - Clinton Impeachment Trial, 1986-1999; 1.
    The Clinton Impeachment Trial subseries includes information on President William J. Clinton's 1998-1999 impeachment trial by the Senate. The materials are arranged alphabetically by topic, and include reports, hearing transcripts, background information, and Congressional Records.
    - Background, 1998-1999 (Box 479, Folder 1-2)
    - Clinton response to Articles of Impeachment, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Judiciary impeachment inquiry, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 4-5)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, Part 1, September 18, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 7)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, Part 2, September 18, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 8)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, Part 1, September 28, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 9)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, Part 2, September 28, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 10)
    - Communication with Kenneth W. Starr, Independent Counsel, Part 3, September 28, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 11)
    - Congressional communications, 1998-1999 (Box 479, Folder 12)
    - Congressional Records, 1998-1999 (Box 479, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Records and Resolutions, 1999 (Box 479, Folder 14)
    - Constituent mail, 1998-1999 (Box 479, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 479, Folder 16)
    - Evidence, 1999 (Box 479, Folder 17)
    - Evidence binder, 1997-1999 (Box 480, Folder 1-4)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. I-II, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 5)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. III, Part 1, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 6)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. III, Part 2, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 7)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. IV, Part 1, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 8)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. IV, Part 3, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 9)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. V-VII, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 10)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. VIII-IX, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 11)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. X, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 12)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XI, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 13)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XII, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 1)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XIII, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 2)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XIV, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 3)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XV, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 4)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. XVI-XVIII, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 5)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vol. XIX, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 6)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. XX-XXI, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 7)
    - Evidentiary Record, Vols. XXII-XXIV, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 8)
    - Government intranet reports, 1998-1999 (Box 481, Folder 9)
    - Independent Counsel and Department of Justice, 1998 (Box 481, Folder 10)
    - Inquiry, 1998 (Box 481, Folder 11)
    - Memos, 1997 (Box 481, Folder 12)
    - Memos, 1998 (Box 481, Folder 13)
    - Memos, 1999 (Box 481, Folder 14)
    - Memos and transcripts, 1998-1999 (Box 481, Folder 15)
    - Notes, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - Notes and trial plans, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - Notes and trial statement drafts, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 3-4)
    - Precedents, 1986-1989 (Box 482, Folder 5)
    - Precedents and preparation, 1998-1999 (Box 482, Folder 6)
    - Press, 1996 (Box 482, Folder 7)
    - Press, 1998 (Box 482, Folder 8)
    - Press, 1998-1999 (Box 482, Folder 9-10)
    - Press, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 11)
    - Procedure, 1986-1998 (Box 482, Folder 12)
    - Records binder, 1998-1999 (Box 482, Folder 13-14)
    - Scots Law research, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 15)
    - Timeline binder, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 16)
    - Trial documents, Appendix to Trial Memorandum of President Clinton, 1999 (Box 482, Folder 17)
    - Trial documents, Appendix to Trial Memorandum of President Clinton, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Trial documents, Clinton Memorandum, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Trial documents, Committee on the Judiciary reports, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 3-4)
    - Trial documents, Depositions, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 5-6)
    - Trial documents, Evidence submitted, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 7)
    - Trial documents, Factual records, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 8-15)
    - Trial documents, Memorandum of the House of Representatives, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 16)
    - Trial documents, Memorandum of the House of Representatives, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 1)
    - Trial documents, Motion, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 2)
    - Trial documents, Kenneth Starr statement, 1998-1999 (Box 484, Folder 3-4)
    - Trial documents, Transcript, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 5)
    - Trial documents, Transcripts and filing, 1998-1999 (Box 484, Folder 6-7)
    - Trial documents, White House exhibits, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 8)
    - Trial research, 1998-1999 (Box 484, Folder 9-11)
    - Trial research and reports, 1998-1999 (Box 484, Folder 12)
    - Trial statements and presentations, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 13-14)
    - Washington Post excerpts, 1999 (Box 484, Folder 15)
  - Floor Statements, 1981-2009; 2.
    The Floor Statements subseries contains a record of Senator Specter's statements on the Senate floor from 1981 through 2009. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - 1981 (Box 485, Folder 1)
    - February-June 1982 (Box 485, Folder 2)
    - July-December 1982 (Box 485, Folder 3)
    - January-May 1983 (Box 485, Folder 4)
    - June-September 1983 (Box 485, Folder 5)
    - October-December 1983 (Box 485, Folder 6)
    - January-May 1984 (Box 485, Folder 7)
    - June-October 1984 (Box 485, Folder 8)
    - January-March 1985 (Box 485, Folder 9)
    - April-June 1985 (Box 485, Folder 10)
    - July-December 1985 (Box 485, Folder 11)
    - January-May 1986 (Box 485, Folder 12)
    - June-October 1986 (Box 485, Folder 13)
    - January-May 1987 (Box 486, Folder 1)
    - June-December 1987 (Box 486, Folder 2)
    - February-March 1988 (Box 486, Folder 3)
    - April-May 1988 (Box 486, Folder 4)
    - June-November 1988 (Box 486, Folder 5)
    - January-May 1989 (Box 486, Folder 6)
    - June-November 1989 (Box 486, Folder 7)
    - January-April 1990 (Box 486, Folder 8)
    - May-August 1990 (Box 486, Folder 9)
    - September-October 1990 (Box 486, Folder 10)
    - January-March 1991 (Box 486, Folder 11)
    - April-June 1991 (Box 486, Folder 12)
    - July-September 1991 (Box 486, Folder 13)
    - October-November 1991 (Box 486, Folder 14)
    - January-April 1992 (Box 487, Folder 1)
    - May-August 1992 (Box 487, Folder 2)
    - September-October 1992 (Box 487, Folder 3)
    - January-March 1993 (Box 487, Folder 4)
    - April-August 1993 (Box 487, Folder 5)
    - September 1993 (Box 487, Folder 6)
    - October-November 1993 (Box 487, Folder 7)
    - January-June 1994 (Box 487, Folder 8)
    - July-November 1994 (Box 487, Folder 9)
    - January-May 1995 (Box 487, Folder 10)
    - June-December 1995 (Box 487, Folder 11)
    - January-July 1996 (Box 487, Folder 12)
    - August-October 1996 (Box 487, Folder 13)
    - January-June 1997 (Box 487, Folder 14)
    - July-November 1997 (Box 488, Folder 1)
    - January-April 1998 (Box 488, Folder 2)
    - May-October 1998 (Box 488, Folder 3)
    - January-March 1999 (Box 488, Folder 4)
    - April-July 1999 (Box 488, Folder 5)
    - August-November 1999 (Box 488, Folder 6)
    - 2000 (Box 488, Folder 7)
    - January-July 2001 (Box 488, Folder 8)
    - August-November 2001 (Box 488, Folder 9)
    - 2002 (Box 488, Folder 10)
    - January-August 2003 (Box 488, Folder 11)
    - September-December 2003 (Box 488, Folder 12)
    - 2004 (Box 488, Folder 13)
    - January-September 2005 (Box 488, Folder 14)
    - October-December 2005 (Box 488, Folder 15)
    - January-April 2006 (Box 488, Folder 16)
    - May-December 2006 (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - 2007 (Box 489, Folder 2)
    - 2008 (Box 489, Folder 3)
    - 2009 (Box 489, Folder 4)
  - Voting Records, 1981-2005; 3.
    The Voting Records subseries contains Senator Specter's recorded votes on issues from 1981 to 2005. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - January-May 1981 (Box 490, Folder 1)
    - June-September 1981 (Box 490, Folder 2)
    - October-November 1981 (Box 490, Folder 3)
    - December 1981-February 1982 (Box 490, Folder 4)
    - March-May 1982 (Box 490, Folder 5)
    - July-August 1982 (Box 490, Folder 6)
    - September-December 1982 (Box 490, Folder 7)
    - February-May 1983 (Box 490, Folder 8)
    - June-July 1983 (Box 490, Folder 9)
    - August-November 1983 (Box 490, Folder 10)
    - January-June 1984 (Box 490, Folder 11)
    - July-October 1984 (Box 490, Folder 12)
    - February-June 1985 (Box 490, Folder 13)
    - November-December 1985 (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - January-May 1986 (Box 491, Folder 2)
    - June-August 1986 (Box 491, Folder 3)
    - September-October 1986 (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - January-April 1987 (Box 491, Folder 5)
    - May-July 1987 (Box 491, Folder 6)
    - August-October 1987 (Box 491, Folder 7)
    - November 1987-February 1988 (Box 491, Folder 8)
    - March-May 1988 (Box 491, Folder 9)
    - June-August 1988 (Box 491, Folder 10)
    - September 1988-May 1989 (Box 491, Folder 11)
    - June-September 1989 (Box 491, Folder 12)
    - October 1989-March 1990 (Box 491, Folder 13)
    - April-June 1990 (Box 492, Folder 1)
    - July-September 1990 (Box 492, Folder 2)
    - October 1990-March 1991 (Box 492, Folder 3)
    - April-July 1991 (Box 492, Folder 4)
    - August-November 1991 (Box 492, Folder 5)
    - January-May 1992 (Box 492, Folder 6)
    - June-October 1992 (Box 492, Folder 7)
    - November 1992-February 1993 (Box 492, Folder 8)
    - March-April 1993 (Box 492, Folder 9)
    - May-July 1993 (Box 492, Folder 10)
    - August-October 1993 (Box 492, Folder 11)
    - November 1993-January 1994 (Box 492, Folder 12)
    - January-April 1994 (Box 492, Folder 13)
    - May-June 1994 (Box 492, Folder 14)
    - July-August 1994 (Box 493, Folder 1)
    - September 1994-April 1995 (Box 493, Folder 2)
    - May 1995 (Box 493, Folder 3)
    - June-August 1995 (Box 493, Folder 4)
    - September 1995 (Box 493, Folder 5)
    - October-November 1995 (Box 493, Folder 6)
    - December 1995-March 1996 (Box 493, Folder 7)
    - April-May 1996 (Box 493, Folder 8)
    - June-August 1996 (Box 493, Folder 9)
    - September 1996-April 1997 (Box 493, Folder 10)
    - May-September 1997 (Box 493, Folder 11)
    - October 1997-March 1998 (Box 493, Folder 12)
    - April-May 1998 (Box 493, Folder 13)
    - June-September 1998 (Box 493, Folder 14)
    - October 1998-April 1999 (Box 494, Folder 1)
    - August-December 1999 (Box 494, Folder 2)
    - January-May 2000 (Box 494, Folder 3)
    - June-September 2000 (Box 494, Folder 4)
    - October 2000-April 2001 (Box 494, Folder 5)
    - May-June 2001 (Box 494, Folder 6)
    - July-November 2001 (Box 494, Folder 7)
    - December 2001-June 2002 (Box 494, Folder 8)
    - July 2002-January 2003 (Box 494, Folder 9)
    - February-March 2003 (Box 494, Folder 10)
    - April-May 2003 (Box 494, Folder 11)
    - June-August 2003 (Box 494, Folder 12)
    - September-October 2003 (Box 495, Folder 1)
    - November 2003-February 2004 (Box 495, Folder 2)
    - March-May 2004 (Box 495, Folder 3)
    - June-December 2004 (Box 495, Folder 4)
    - January-March 2005 (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - April-June 2005 (Box 495, Folder 6)
    - July-October 2005 (Box 495, Folder 7)